Well, it's started, Upokami. This time we are joined by Kanami Ishiguri of Ochanoma and Akari Endo of Juice-Juice.
This is a program that takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the up-front group.
We will show you our recording, rehearsal and other production processes.
Now, as we start the year 2024, I would like to talk about our goals for this year and what we would like to do our best for.
Yes, I am Ishiguri.
I, Ishiguri, will turn 20 years old on April 20, 2024, so I would like to show a more mature look than when I was a teenager, but I am still only 20 years old, so I would like to do my best while also showing a little freshness.
Yes, I am 20 years old, and I think it is a time for me to change my mind,
I don't know what to say. Please do your best.
Thank you very much. You have my support. I will do my best.
I'm cheering for you.
Thank you.
Yes, thank you very much. I, Sonofuji, would like to make a lot of memories with Ms. Akari Uemura before she graduates in the spring.
Also, I will be a high school student from April, so I will do my best as an adult. From now on.
I see. You are still a high school student? So you are still in the third year of junior high school?
That's right.
Good luck in high school. I'll do my best. Let's work hard for each other.
But you know, I am very sad to hear that you are graduating, too,
I hope I can make many memories at the Hello Project concert in winter.
Let's start with this up-date.
Angelem Life is Beautiful Music Video Making of the Shooting
The newest single of Angulum, "Life is Beautiful" was released on December 13th. The music video for "Life is Beautiful" from Angulum's latest single
Please take a look at the making of the music video for "Life is Beautiful".
Up! Kami! It's starting!
The music video for "Life is Beautiful" is being filmed.
Here's what the costumes look like.
How do you like it?
The costume maker put a patch on it that says "Life is Beautiful.
I'm so happy. It's so cute.
I'm really looking forward to a fun day of shooting.
It's going to be like this.
I'm going to be moving in and out of the photo shoot,
It's a little bit like this.
It's great.
You can say, "Wow, wow, wow, wow!
You can say, "Wow!
It's okay to play around with it.
Look forward to the next time!
I have never held a steering wheel at all, so I'm trying to figure out how to hold it. I have never held a steering wheel at all, so I am trying to figure out how I should hold the steering wheel.
I'm trying to figure out what kind of grip I should use for the scene where the camera is attached to the steering wheel and it looks like I'm driving,
It's rare to have a lip scene with props like this,
I'd like to do my best to make it look like a driving scene.
I'd like to do my best to make it look like I'm driving.
Are you spinning?
Unlike the previous Red Line, this time's song is about having a lot of fun,
I'm going to have a lot of fun myself.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm not so much nervous.
I don't know why.
Um...
I knew I'm not good at drowning my toilets.
It's just such an excuse now, but...
But...
It's a little difficult.
I have one thing in the back of my mind
But I'm going to have to have fun with it.
It's going to be fun!
[ED]
Good day to you, please watch again.
Can I ask you two to step up to the camera and sing first?
Yes!
Yes! Sound!
Sound!
Let's hear you two sing!
Okkun, it's fun.
I want to get to know you better.
A little jealousy goes a long way.
I'll be brave, I'll be global warming
I've had enough for one day.
I'm not going to let today's date get away from me
It's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good.
Yay!
Yay Yeah!
Here you go, cut.
You.
Matter released.
Please wait
Yeah!
I want to love you, I want to be in love with you, I want to be in love with you
I can't decide which one I want.
I want to love you, I want to love you, I want to love you, I can't decide which one I want.
Come on, ski, yuki
Come on, Mac, low kick
Catch line, timing for bed
Catch line, fish roe
I'll be right there.
Let's party, runner, see you today
Easy to overdo, guest.
Wait! Softly, cab! Today's overdose!
Things are piled up, but there's nothing inside.
It's head night!
Oh, what a fun ride!
I'm gonna hit the angels on the reef key
I'm having the time of my life. I'm having the time of my life. I'm having the time of my life.
It's pretty fulfilling. It's a lot of fun.
Yeah, you totally get the game.
It's okay to screw up big time.
You get to be so good that you regret it.
No matter how bad it is.
Let's make love, let's make love, let's make love, let's make love, let's make love
To the chandelier that rides on the wind
It's important
Yes, this song is a fun song for the other Red Line, the first single for the two of us,
I can see the two's innocent brightness and so on,
It's a fun song, so you can see their innocent brightness, but also Anchan's usual goodness inside,
It is filled with An-chan's usual goodness and vividness,
I think we were able to create a music video that I hope people will pay attention to.
It was already summer.
It was summer.
It was summer. It really was. It was summer. Really.
There was a lot of car use and driving,
There were a lot of comical parts,
I thought, "This is the kind of music that has this kind of atmosphere,
I think it's going to be another interesting music video.
RinRin is also a highlight here.
Mr. Sasaki came up with the idea for this dance.
The atmosphere was completely different from the last time we shot Red Line,
The feel of the song is also different,
The feel of the shoot was different, and the location was totally different,
I thought it was a lot of fun.
The outside shooting,
The colors of the outside, the location, etc,
I thought that the color of the outside, the location, etc,
I thought it was interesting,
It was interesting.
I think it really captures the sparkle of the two of them.
Look at this.
See it!
Se-no, abukami sara-bye.
Yes, I have seen the making of the music video shoot, and I was impressed by the euphoric and happy feeling of Angsturm, and I thought everyone was very cute.
That handle? I was surprised at how it moved with the camera.
I was surprised at how it moved with the camera. There were some members who were actually using it for the first time in a music video, and they all looked so cute.
I was impressed by how well they did it. This is the making of the shooting for the music video of Life is Beautiful by Angulum.
How are you?
Next, here is a video of Morning Musume。 Morning Musume。 23 Wake up call Waking up vocal recording
The latest single from Morning Musume。 23's latest single, Wake up call Awakening Time, please take a look at the vocal recording of Mizuki Fukumura.
We'll start with the A melody and work our way up in blocks.
As I said before, we're going for a bit of a strong flavor with a strong character.
So we're not going to sing in a normal way.
It's a little strong.
That's right.
That kind of makeup doesn't suit you. It's not a habit. It's a quality of femininity.
It'll be more interesting.
I understand.
Then let's try it. Then let's do it.
I'll try it. - Okay.
You don't look good in that makeup. It's an imposition of femininity that can't be erased.
Unfortunately, it's not for you. That's all I'm saying.
That's good, that's good, that's good, that's good, that's good, that's good. You could deform it a little more.
For you, I could be a little more self-voiced.
But it's in C, so it should be more self-voiced than you think.
It's a little bit rattly. I'm gonna mix it up a little bit.
Let's mix it up as much as possible.
I'll mix it up as much as I can.
I'm not doing this for you. That's all I'm trying to say.
I'll shoot another one for the second half.
Just that... just that... just that...
It's just that... it's just that...
Yeah, just a little clearer with the words there.
That's all I'm saying.
The imposition of femininity that can't be erased with a laugh
I'm sorry, I'm not doing it for you.
That's all I'm saying.
OK, I'll take it then
Let's see, the second half of the A melody
Let's try it once.
Uh, you know, just be a little sharp, and the rest will be fine.
Cute, cool, mawkish, dramatic.
Maybe a little accent after that.
I'm not trying to be a dick to you, that's all I'm trying to say.
I just want you to be cute and cool, and I'll give you a little accent after that.
I'm a perennial creature, whatever the fuck that is, and I have to say yes already.
Yeah, it's all good, though.
I do have one request, though.
Cute, cool, mawkish, and charming.
Let's change it up a bit.
Just those four lines, please.
Okay, I think that's good. Let's try the first chorus.
I don't want to trick you.
I don't want to fool me.
It's time to enjoy life
The sun is here in my heart The sun is here, in my heart
Just do me!
I'll shine it for you
Dance baby!
I chewed this heart
I think I can do this
It's gonna be okay.
It's time, isn't it?
It's better to say it in your own voice
My eyes glaze over.
It's a C sharp, so it's kind of subtle.
But if you can get away with it, it's probably cooler to do it in your own voice.
I don't want to cheat.
Wake up call. It's time to wake up.
It's time to enjoy life
The sun is in my heart
Dance baby dance all night dance
My body's doing what it's supposed to do
But my voice is still there.
I'm sorry, I went to the wardrobe room.
Shall we go on then?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Okay, we'll go on from there.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's time to have some fun. The sun is in my heart.
Just do me, just do me, just do me
Just do me! Save me!
Save me!
OK, I'll take a picture of you when I'm done.
Okay!
Someone's heart at the bottom of the night, waiting for morning
Just do me!
I'm going to record the falsetto and the lower octave of "Waiting for Morning.
I'll start with the higher octave.
At the bottom of the night, I can do it myself.
The point is, at the bottom of the night.
The point is, at the bottom of the night, when you get back to your own voice...
And then you go back to the falsetto, and that's the best part. It's rather a real pleasure to suddenly go to a fal
Someone's heart at the bottom of the night, waiting for the morning.
I think it's interesting to switch between the two.
I think it's interesting to switch between the two, so please give it a try.
Let's start with someone's heart waiting for morning.
Someone's heart waiting for morning
Yes, I got it.
Here you go.
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
So it's a wrap.
It's okay, right? I'm good, I'm good, I'm good.
The Beat is oblivious.
I'm going to have to make up my mind on that one.
Okay, let's do it again.
You can't know 10 minutes at the barn. You can't know it when you've been through it all your life.
People have to be a little kinder. You can't even recognize the real The Fee if you give up on it.
Great, we're on a roll.
Good, good, good.
Okay, I got it.
I'll take that.
Dramatic background music.
I think I'm getting some interesting pictures.
I'm making this face... it's embarrassing.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's good.
I can't sing otherwise
I think it's good
A foundation created by history
Hand in hand, we've created a formation
I'll raise you up, life's motivation
A little bit stronger.
Yes, sir.
Sound ignites the wind
Dance Baby Dance Baby Dance Baby Dance Baby
Hey, adventure's over Wake up Go!
We're Wake up Go!
Boring's not waking up
It's up to you. Come here.
History has created a Foundation
Formation that we created hand in hand
I'll give you the motivation for life Let's dance
Dance Dance Dance Dance Dance
That's good.
Okay.
Okay, we're done. Thank you very much.
Yes, well, the song "Makeup Call When You Wake Up" is really cool.
I like it so much that I often listen to it at home.
I like it so much that I often listen to it at home... but the way Mr. Fukumura changed his voice during the "cute and cool" part was really cool and cute... and it was very short...
It's so short that it makes all the difference, isn't it?
I thought it was really cool how he sang once and then immediately switched to another part.
Yes, I, Ishiguri, really love this song, just like Akari, and I listen to it a lot at home.
I love this song as much as Akari-chan does, and I listen to it at home, but when I saw the video of Mr. Fukumura's recording, I realized that it is really a difficult song to sing alone.
But as Akari said, "I really digested what I was asked to do immediately.
I thought it was really cool that you were able to digest what you were told and sang it right away.
I thought it was really cool and I learned a lot from it.
That's all for Morning Musume。 23 Bake Up Call When You Wake Up" was the vocal recording of Mizuki Fukumura.
Let's do our best again tomorrow!
Here's another up-cam by Kami Ishigiri of Ochanoma and Akari Endo of JuiceJuice!
JuiceJuice Bon Voyage Miracle of Thoughts Vocal Recording
Here's a look at the vocal recording of JuiceJuice's latest album Bon Voyage - The Miracle of Thoughts by Ichika Arisawa!
Let's get to it! Let's do it then!
First of all, let's go to MUK.
Thank you for watching.
I'm back in my favorite town, strolling with my new friends.
The changing times made me realize where I want to go and my unchanging dreams.
Can I smile more?
Yes, please.
I'm back in my favorite town, strolling with more friends
The changing times made me realize where I want to go and my unchanging dreams
OK, that's good. Okay, let's go to number 1, B melody.
I made you realize where you want to go and the dreams that won't change
We overcame those dreary days together
Because we got over it
I don't care what storms come my way, even if my heels wear out and the mud splashes on me
I'll walk with you all, and I'm not afraid of the maze
Cause the light's shining and it's pulling me along
We'll make our way through the road less traveled
Well, it's like this...
Juice juice juice, all of you...
Or we can do it with Sanfra
We can all walk together like this...
Yay! Let's go! something like that.
That's what I'm thinking of.
Let's go!
Please do!
I'm not afraid of storms.
Worn heels
Mud bouncing off my heels
With all of you
I'll walk on foot
I'm not afraid of the maze
Because the light shines on me and pulls me through
And pulled me along
We're going to make our way
Let's carve it out
Here we go.
Yeah, now dash 3C
3C dash 3C Dash.
Let's go with that ending
We'll share everything with one heart
We'll pile it up and turn it into a tailwind
I'm not afraid of the maze, next time I'll pull you along
Let's cut through the road without a path
Let's talk about the miracle of our hearts
Yes, yes, you're doing a great job with the flow of the song.
The last part
Yes, yes.
Let's tell the story
And, um...
It's just the way it ends.
Ha-ha-ha.
You're trying to end it, and it's ending.
So you don't have to think about ending it.
You don't have to think about ending it.
Just end it without thinking about ending it.
Yes, sir.
I don't care what kind of storm it is
If there's a port with true feelings
I can see the end of the rainbow
I'm going after it
We can share it all
One heart to wish for
I'm sorry, sir.
You're the cheat doll of the first place?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Did you have chopsticks like these?
I'm sorry.
They were micros.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry... one more time, please.
You were singing so well.
I made a mistake. I'm sorry.
We can share everything with one heart
We'll pile it up and turn it into a tailwind
I'm not afraid of the maze, next time I'll pull you along I'm not afraid of the maze, next time I'll pull you through
Let's make our way through the road less traveled
Let's tell the story of our feelings
Yeah, you know, it's okay, but that wrong take you just did was really good.
I'm sorry you had to hear that.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, but if it was so good earlier, why did you say this?
I'm sorry, I just thought it wasn't right.
I don't know, it's like, "That was the best take.
I'm sorry.
Let's do it again.
Please do.
Thank you very much.
We can share everything with one heart
We will overlap and turn into a tailwind
I'm not afraid of the maze, next time I'll pull you along
Let's cut through the road without a path
Let's make a trail of our thoughts and feelings.
Okay, is that okay?
Okay.
Okay, I guess that's all for this song, then.
Okay. Thank you very much.
This song, Bon Voyage: Miracle of Souls, is very positive,
As the director said, the lyrics are about walking together in a positive way,
It is a very moving song, so when this song was performed at the Nippon Budokan, I cried during the performance.
I was so moved by this song that I cried when I heard it at the Nippon Budokan,
Bon voyage: Miracle of Souls is the latest song on the album,
The other songs were newly recorded with the current members, so I think they have a different atmosphere from the original members, so please listen to them.
Yes, look at the recording of Arisaha Ichika-chan,
I really love the way she sings with emotion in her voice,
Even with my eyes closed, I could see her expression in her singing, and I could really feel it in the recording.
This was the vocal recording of JuiceJuice Bon Voyage: The Miracle of Thoughts by Arisaha Ichika.
Everyone is surely wishing for a wonderful future.
But now I want a phrase or two from you
You can do it
It's time to say goodbye to the up-dated paper that has been sent by Kosui Ishiguri and Akari Endo!
Now, we've seen various videos this time too, but I, Endo, really enjoyed Ichika Arisawa's recording.
I'm also listening to it for the first time, so now my part is pretty much split up. I also listened to it for the first time when you taught me this song. I'm listening to this song for the first time, so I'm splitting up the parts now. When I first heard this song, I thought it was a pretty quiet song.
When I first heard the song, I thought it was going to be a pretty quiet song, but the lyrics are very positive, so I was told to sing it in a groove, and I was reminded of that.
I remembered that when I heard you sing it.
I, Ishiguri, remember the recording of Mizuki Fukumura's vocal.
I still can't get it out of my mind, but I think this must be the last video of Mizuki Fukumura's recording as Morning Musume san.
I'm sure this will be the last recording video of Mizuki Fukumura as Morning Musume san.
I'm so happy that I was able to see something so precious.
UpCami will take you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the UpFront Group.
This time, our up-cam partners are Kanami Ishigiri of Ochanoma and Akari Endo of Juice-Juice.
Good bye!
Next time on Upkami: Morning Musume。 23 Gake Up Call: When I Wake Up Dance Lesson
And we will be showing the recording of Angulum Red Line.
Enjoy!
This kiss is proof of my readiness
I do I do I'll only show it to you